<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on LLVM Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.llvm.org/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on LLVM Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://foundation.llvm.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Board of Directors</title><link>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/board/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/board/</guid><description>Board of Directors The Board of Directors consists of 8 members serving 2 year terms, which then elect the next set of board members. In terms of time commitment, the board typically meets every month for 2 hours and every board member should plan on attending each meeting. At times a board member will take lead on a particular issue, doing the background research needed, forming a proposal, bringing to the Board for productive discussion and vote.</description></item><item><title>Branch Renaming</title><link>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/branch-rename/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/branch-rename/</guid><description>Renaming Default Branch to &amp;lsquo;Main&amp;rsquo; Many tech communities, including GitHub and Git, have moved away from the term “master branch” and replaced it with “main branch” in an effort to remove unnecessary references to slavery and use more inclusive terms. This was also discussed on the LLVM-dev mailing list and there was strong consensus from LLVM Developers’ that the LLVM Project should also rename our master branch as well. Now that an industry standard name has been selected by GitHub, the LLVM Project can begin the renaming process of the default branch to “main”.</description></item><item><title>Infrastructure Working Group</title><link>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/infrastructure-wg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/infrastructure-wg/</guid><description>Infrastructure Working Group (in the course of formation) The infrastructure working group (IWG) understands the needs and pains of the community and shapes the project infrastructure to meet these needs.
Note: This page is an initial proposal. We will improve our setup and work mode as we go along and gain experience.
Scope The working group will work on the LLVM project infrastructure including:
source code repository bug tracker build servers/machines web sites build system/scripts code review tool mailing lists internet forum chat Documentation of the tools and their work flows.</description></item><item><title>Public Documents</title><link>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/finance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/finance/</guid><description>LLVM Foundation Financial Documents This section contains all the Monthly and Annual Financial Reports published by the Foundation.
Monthly Financial Reports 2020 ... November 2020 ... * [Budget Detail](/documents/finance/statements/2020/11_November/LLVM_Foundation_-_Budget_Detail.pdf) * [Monthly Reports](/documents/finance/statements/2020/11_November/LLVM_Foundation_-_Monthly_Reports.pdf) October 2020 ... * [Budget Detail](/documents/finance/statements/2020/10_October/LLVM_Foundation_-_Budget_Detail.pdf) * [Monthly Reports](/documents/finance/statements/2020/10_October/LLVM_Foundation_-_Monthly_Reports.pdf) September 2020 ... * [Budget Detail](/documents/finance/statements/2020/9_September/LLVM_Foundation_-_Budget_Detail.pdf) * [Monthly Reports](/documents/finance/statements/2020/9_September/LLVM_Foundation_-_Monthly_Reports.pdf) August 2020 .</description></item><item><title>Public Documents</title><link>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/public-docs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/public-docs/</guid><description>LLVM Foundation Documents Here you find all important documents related to the LLVM Foundation governance, board meeting minutes, tax exemption status, and tax returns.
Governance Articles of Incorporation
Bylaws
Conflict of Interest Policy
Board Meeting Minutes 2021 ... December 8, 2021
November 3, 2021
October 1, 2021
September 3, 2021</description></item><item><title>Relicensing</title><link>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/relicensing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/relicensing/</guid><description>LLVM Relicensing Effort The LLVM relicensing effort aims to modernize the LLVM Licensing structure and developer policy. The high level goals of the relicensing effort are to:
Encourage ongoing contributions to LLVM by preserving a low barrier to entry for contributors Protect users of LLVM code by providing explicit patent protection in the license Protect contributors to the LLVM project by explicitly scoping their patent contributions with this license Eliminate the schism between runtime libraries and the rest of the compiler that makes it difficult to move code between them Ensure that LLVM runtime libraries may be used by other open source and proprietary compilers This project involves sensitive legal issues and has been a multi-year effort.</description></item><item><title>Relicensing Long Tail</title><link>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/relicensing_long_tail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/relicensing_long_tail/</guid><description>Long tail of individuals and corporations without a relicensing agreement yet The LLVM relicensing effort is currently at the stage where we collect agreements from individuals and corporations owning the copyright of contributions before 19th of January 2019.
We already have agreements in place for the far majority of contributions. We still have a long tail of both individuals and corporations we&amp;rsquo;d like to get agreements from.
The list of individuals and corporations we&amp;rsquo;d still like to get agreements from is regularly updated in a spreadsheet.</description></item><item><title>Sponsors</title><link>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/sponsors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.llvm.org/docs/sponsors/</guid><description>Sponsors Join our sponsors!
Diamond Sponsors Apple
QuIC
Platinum Sponsors Google
Fastly
IBM
Gold Sponsors ARM
Intel
Access Softek, Inc.
Synopsys
Facebook
Huawei
Sony Interactive Entertainment</description></item></channel></rss>